

JURE EREŠ FRONT-ENDDEVELOPER

INFO

+385915735157

jure.eres42@gmail.com



B category

LINKS

Portfolio site Github LinkedIn SoloLearn

LANGUAGES

Croatian English

Danish

PERSONALITY

Interested in ideas, and exploring different opinions, when its time to work I like to be brief and get the job done best we can as a team. Love good time-work and light atmosphere. More then 5 years work experience. The most important guide line for me is honesty.

//All of my projects are in portfolio with descriptions and

WORK EXPERIENCE

AMAZON AFFILIATE Self-employed

Jan 2016 - Nov 2016

- SEO, website creation, visual site optimization, simple back-end
- marketing, product research, market research
- tools: website bilder, host provider, HTML, CSS, JS

IT EQUIPMENT SALES CONSULTANT Hangar 18 d.o.o.

May 2019 - Oct 2019

- computer maintenance, assembly, systems installation and setup
- work at the registry, sale face2face, IT goods consultant
- database operation (luceed), work in Windows Office sistem

TS AGENT FOR BUSINESS CLIENTS A1 Hrvatska

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

- database work (siebel), work in Windows Office sistem
- negotiations on existing and new services, care for existing users
- regular contact with existing clients, concluding business cooperation

EDUCATION HISTORY

FRONT END DEVELOPER Algebra University College, Zagreb

Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

In short React, Redux, JavaScript, Node.js, HTML and CSS in depth. We have learned how to set up and develop web application from the ground up. All projects from this, my own and from other ventures are in my portfolio.

HOBBIES

Mountain biking - riding a bicycle trough forest for the soul Gym and swimming for healthy body:)

I have started learning Danish in February this year, it's very complex but interesting language, and have learned some German while in elementary school, but I'm a bit rusty there.

Gamer in heart.

COURSES

SoloLearn

- Hyper Text Markup Language certificate
- Cascading Style Sheets certificate
- JavaScript certificate
- Web Development Fundamentals certificate
- Responsive Web Design certificate

SKILS

INDUSTRIAL SKILS

- React
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Git
- jQuery
- Googling

- HTML & CSS
- Sass
- Less
- Bootstrap
- SQL
- Angular

TEAM SKILS

- Ability to Work in a Team
- Effective Time Management
- Microsoft Office environment
- Communication Skills
- Adaptability
- Creativity

INSPIRATION

//As you can probably guess I really like to code, so I decided to show
my personality trough thing I love to do, hope You like it:)

export default Task